{
    "id": "b6d18eaf24d74a50960025186fbfcea2",
    "title": "Since And For Worksheet",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I have been waiting for the guests …………….. morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ab16438fee094a7e951fa34783742165"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has been suffering from fever ………………. Monday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9855b791778f4324932383431bef7a43"
        },
        {
            "question": "It has been raining heavily …………….. last night.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "682be597320c425d879eeaf02128d4d0"
        },
        {
            "question": "My father has been serving in the army …………….. 20 years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d1fd3a9764a3480cb33362647f2a61d8"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has not been attending the school ……………… last Monday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2020e8ed6c5b46b6b3c09d5251aa6c31"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have been teaching in this college ……………. 10 years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "48cf05d9023a440a9a9647739dab98a6"
        },
        {
            "question": "The masons have been building this house ………………. last March.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6fa646285e04444cb580921e47d67aa7"
        },
        {
            "question": "Man has been struggling against the forces of nature ………………. times immemorial.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1a24ce59a5af4df0b16d0f77d42f3400"
        },
        {
            "question": "A cold breeze has been blowing ……………….. yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0e37f1c24d55462894d15f25bfedb711"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has been doing his homework …………… .. 4 o’clock.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "81b1f2287e454ee89a157263a0b4c4d2"
        }
    ]
}